Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series I. 1963-1965
  - HO-HZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Holley, Robert W.; Holmes, Oliver W.
  - HO-HZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Kurd, T. Norman; Durling, Robert M.; Humphrey, Hubert H.; Huber Foundation; Cornell University Humanities Council.
  - United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Celebreeze, Anthony.
  - I Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    IBM; International Honors Program.
  - Invitations - Ithaca., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 39-41)
  - Invitations - Out of Town., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 42-45)
  - International Association of Universities., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    University autonomy.
  - City of Ithaca., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    Johns, Hunna; Ryan, John F.
  - Ithaca Festival., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 48-49)
    Javits, Jacob K.; Schneider, Alan; Zeigler, J. Wesley.
  - J Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    James, F. Cyril; MacKinnon, A. Donald; Johnson, Samuel C.; Javits, Jacob K.; Kahin, George McT. James Foundation; Johnson Foundation.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Kac, Mark; Olum, Paul; Morris, Emory W.; Kahn, Peter; Keating, Kenneth B.; Keppel, Francis. W.K. Kellogg Foundation; Humanities Council.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Kennedy, Robert F.; Kennedy, John F.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Kirk, Grayson; Kiddoo, Gordon; Kilmer, Harold C.; Kinne, Birge W.; Keppel, Francis; Kahn, Peter; Keating, Kenneth B. Peace Research Library.
  - K Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Konvitz, Milton R.; Kottman, Roy M.; Krebs, A. Sonnin.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Lall, Arthur; Larson, Olaf F.; Ransom, Harry. Institute of Latin-American Studies.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Levitsky, Asher S. Cornell University at the University of Liberia; Agency for International Development.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Linowitz, Sol M.; Luckey, E. Hugh. Lincoln Center Week.
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Lynn, John S.; Templeton, Kenneth S.; Noyes, Nicholas H. CURW.
  - MA-MF Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Mahoney, Walter J.; Malott, Deane W.; Marcham, Frederick G.; Maresh, James I.
  - MA-MF Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Matousek, Otakar; Mennen, William G.; McConnell, T.R.; Medawar, Peter B.
  - MG-MZ Miscellaneous. Mizener, Arthur M.; Peach, Robert E., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - MG-MZ Miscellaneous. Morison, Robert S.; Olin, Spencer T.; Morrison, Philip; Corson, Dale R., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - N Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Nason, John W. University of Nancy; United States Navy.
  - N Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    United States Navy.
  - N Miscellaneous. Quik, H.G.; Newsom, John R.; Lynch, J. Joseph. United States Navy; New York Academy of Sciences; Negro colleges; Negro students., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - N Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Green, Alfred L.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Nimitz, Chester W.; Nimmanheminda, Sukich; Noyes, Agnes B.; Bewkes, Eugene G. Edward John Noble Foundation; New York Academy of Sciences; Experimental College at Cornell University (Proposed).
  - National Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Moore, Geoffrey H.; Webb, James E.; Saltonstall, Leverett. National Academy of Sciences; National Aeronautics and Space Administration; National Humanities Foundation; National Science Foundation.
  - National Commission on Accrediting., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Longnecker, Herbert E.
  - National Education Association., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Newman, Floyd R. Thomas R. Briggs Professorship in Engineering; Floyd Newman Professorship; Helen Newman Hall., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - New York State., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Kurd, T. Norman; Abrams, Albert J.; Metcalf, George R. State of New York Atomic Research and Development Authority; Nuclear power.
  - Noyes, Jansen., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Noyes, Jansen Sr.; Mackesey, Thomas W. Freshmen Center.
  - O Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    O'Brien, Richard D.; Ottinger, Richard L.; Mizener, Arthur M. Old Dominion Foundation.
  - PA-PK Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Panofsky, Erwin; Shriver, Sargent; Parks, Harold F.; Corson, Dale R. Pearsall Estate; Peace Corps; Sierra Leone IV Project.
  - PA-PK Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Perkins, Frances; Pew, J. Howard; Pew, Joseph N.; Pierce, Samuel R.; Phillips, Mary G. Ellis L. Phillips Foundation.
  - PL-PZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Benitez, Jaime.
  - Q Miscellaneous., 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Queeny, Edgar M.
  - Questionnaires., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - RA-RK Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Rebmann, G. Ruhland; Reps, John W.; Ranum, Orest.
  - RA-RK Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Requardt, Gustav J.; Riesman, David. Research Club of Cornell University; Research Institute of America.
  - RL-RZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    Rockwell, George H.; Rogosin, Israel; Burr, David; Romanoff, Alexis L.; Palm, Charles- E.; Clark, John M.; Rebmann, G. Ruhland; Rossiter, Clinton; Robertson, William R. Rogosin Foundation.
  - Roberson Center Growth Fund., 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Wilson, Thomas A. Roberson Memorial Center.
  - Rockefeller Foundation., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Kahin, George McT.; Thompson, Kenneth W.; Mizener, Arthur M.; Ashby, Eric; Harrar, J. George; Smidt, Seymour.
  - SA-SL Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    Salwak, Stanley F.; Demorest, Jean-Jacques, Committee on Institutional Cooperation.
  - SA-SL Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Seymour, Harold J. Jacob Gould Schurman Scholarships.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Statler Foundation.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    Stevens, Stoddard M.; Stevenson, Adlai E.; Steward, Frederick C. Old Dominion Foundation; Avalon Foundation Professorship in the Humanities; Mellon Charitable Trust.
  - SM-SZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Stratton, Julius A.; Summerskill, John. University of Sydney; Student Agencies, Inc.
  - Scholarship Halls., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    Storandt, Peter C. Von Cramm Scholarship Residence Hall Association.
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Case, Everett Needham; Kreidler, Robert N.; Sloan, Alfred P. Computer Science Center.
  - Students in Demonstrations and Aftermath, Spring 1965., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Pemberton, John De J.; Barlow, Mark; Murphy, Royse P.; Malin, Patrick M.; Weill, James D. American Civil Liberties Union; Undergraduate Judiciary Board; University Faculty; Student conduct; Free speech; Student demonstrations; Student protest.
  - Students in Demonstrations and Aftermath, Spring 1965., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    George, Lowell T.; Donlon, Mary H,; Grohmann, H. Victor; Harriman, W. Averell. Undergraduate Judiciary Board; American Civil Liberties Union; Student conduct; Student protest; Student demonstrations.
  - Students in Demonstrations and Aftermath, Spring 1965., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Bradley, Hunt. Undergraduate Judiciary Board; Student conduct; Student protest; Student demonstrations.
  - Students for Education., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Dean, Arthur H. Cornell Daily Sun; Student conduct.
  - TA-TK Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    Taussig, J. Wright; Thant, U. Robert A. Taft Government Institute; Telluride Great Books Program.
  - TL-TZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Tamboulian, Diran H.; Treman, Charles E.; Todd, George L.; Tschebotarioff, Gregory P. Walter H. Todd Trust; Tompkins County Trust Company; Tompkins County United Fund.
  - Teagle Foundation, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Dean, Arthur H.; Josephs, Devereux C.; Mott, Frank E.
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Uihlein, Erwin C.; Stevenson, Adlai E.; Kahin, George McT.; Upson, Maxwell M.; Hutt, W.H. Upson Professorship.
  - U Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Freeman, Orville L.; Wirtz, W. Willard; Upson, Helen R.; Uris, Harold D.; Salet, Eugene A.; Kahin, George McT.; Upson, Maxwell M.
  - V Miscellaneous., 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Vaz, Seferino; Vick, James.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Wade, Harry V.; Kidera, Robert A.; Warren, Earl; Webb, James E.; Wiesner, Jerome B.
  - W Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    White, E.B.; Williams, Robin M.; Wilson, Robert R.; Golay, Frank H.
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series II. 1965-1967
  - Album of photographs and programs from 1965 Centennial, features President Perkins and other VIPs, 1965 (Box 45)
  - By-laws of the University., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Trustee Activities., 1966 (Box 10, Folder S)
    Bess, James L.
  - Trustees A-H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Adams, Morton; Bache, Harold L.; Cisler, Walker L.; Clark, John M. Cornell Fund; Clark Distinguished Teaching Awards; John M. and Emily B. Clark Endowment Fund.
  - Trustees A-H. Collyer, John L.; Donlon, Mary H.; Linowitz, Sol M., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Trustees A-H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Griffis, Stanton; Grohmann, H. Victor; Holland, Jerome H. Louis Hollander Scholarship Fund.
  - Trustees I-P. Johnson, Samuel C.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Kiplinger, Austin H.; Knight, John S.; Linowitz, Sol M. Art museum., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Trustees I-P., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Linowitz, Sol M.; Littlewood, William.
  - Trustees I-P., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Purcell, Robert W.; McMaster, Donald; Newbury, George A. Robert W. Purcell Trust.
  - Trustees Q-Z., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Rogers, Adele; Saperston, Alfred M.; Schoales, Dudley N.; Robertson, William R.
  - Trustees Q-Z. Schoellkopf, Paul A.; Uris, Harold D.; Stewart J.P.; Syme, John P., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Trustees Q-Z., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Will, Philip; Werly, Charles M. University Committee on the Arts.
  - Trustees, General Correspondence., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Belcher, Donald R. Board of Trustees - Committee on Organization and Structure of Board of Trustees; Tuition; Fees.
  - Trustees, General Correspondence., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Dean, Arthur H. University Commission on Residential Environment.
  - Dean, Arthur H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Mackesey, Thomas W. National Science Foundation; Tompkins County Trust Company; Endowment funds; Housing; Memorandum on Borrowing.
  - Dean, Arthur H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Hinsey, Joseph C. College of Arts and Sciences.
  - Dean, Arthur H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Law Schools.
  - Dean, Arthur H*, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; Board of Trustees Executive Committee; Trojan Horse; Dormitories.
  - Dean, Arthur H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Bundy, Me George. Commission on Residential Environment.
  - Governor of New York State., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Dean, Arthur H.
  - Grumann, LeRoy R., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Kingsley, Charles. Grumann Fund; Grumann Squash Courts.
  - Johnson, Herbert F., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Kelly, Burnham. Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art.
  - Levis, J. Preston., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Noyes, Jansen., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Olin, John M.; Long, Franklin A. IBM computer.
  - Noyes, Nicholas H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Tuller, J. Daniel; Rossiter, Clinton; Malott, Deane W. John L. Senior Endowment; Parsons College; Cornell Committee for Balanced Education; Cornell Daily Sun.
  - Olin, John M., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    McCarthy, Stephen A. Orthopedic Foundation for Animals; John M. Olin Foundation; Olin Hall.
  - Olin, John H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Queeny, Edgar M.; Tuller, J. Daniel; Carlson, Eric G. Olin Hall.
  - Olin, Spencer T., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Olin Hall.
  - Scheetz, Francis H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Society for the Humanities.
  - Severinghaus, Leslie R., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    Severinghaus, Sheldon.
  - Upson, Maxwell H., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    Maxwell M. Upson Fund.
  - Wood, Frederic C., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Board of Trustees, Executive Committee., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Board of Trustees, Investment Committee., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 39-41)
  - Board of Trustees, Buildings and Properties Committee., 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 42-43)
  - Board of Trustees, Nominating Committee., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Linowitz, Sol M.; Rockefeller, Laurance S.; Dean, Arthur H.
  - Committee on Organizations and Structure of Board of Trustees., 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Belcher, Donald R.
  - Board of Trustees, Membership Committee., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Purcell, Robert W.
  - Board of Trustees, Finance Committee., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Physical Education and Athletics Board., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Kane, Robert J.
  - Willard Straight Hall, Board of Governors., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Engineering Council., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - New York State College of Agriculture and Experiment Station Council., 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    King, Joseph P.; Palm, Charles E.
  - President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Priority projects; Speeches.
  - President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Priority projects.
  - President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Rockefeller Foundation; Five Year Plans.
  - Deans' Conferences., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Deans and Heads of Departments., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Inter-institutional cooperation.
  - News Bureau., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Tobin, Thomas L.; Dean, Arthur H. Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; Office of Public Information.
  - Correspondence on Academic Freedom., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - News Bureau Releases., 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Assistants to the President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Bess, James L.; McCrimmon, Kent. Housing; Dormitories; Sensitivity training; Planning.
  - Assistants to the President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Bess, James L.; McCrimmon, Kent. American Council on Education; National Training Laboratories; Planning.
  - Assistants to the President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Bess, James L.; Bell, Daniel; Grohmann, H. Victor. Association for Higher Education; Cornell Latin American Year; Course critiques.
  - Priority Projects., 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Town Gown., 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - "Distribution Requirements" Survey., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Reports of the President., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - President's Report., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Staff Meetings Minutes., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 25-27)
  - Staff Meetings Minutes., 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
  - Staff Officers, Circular Notices., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
  - Staff Retreats., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 32-33)
  - Staff Retreats., 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Second Echelon Meetings., 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - President's Office, Employees and Staff., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Mimeographed Notices to Staff., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - President's Speeches., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 38-39)
  - Provost., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    Corson, Dale R.; Mover, Donald H.; Brown, Stuart M.; Kennedy, W. Keith. CURW; Synchrotron; Center for International Studies; Committee on Intercession; Classified research.
  - Provost., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    Corson, Dale R.; Gemmell, Edgar M. James Foundation; SUNY; National Aeronautics and Space Administration; Division of Biological Sciences; Parking; Cornell contributions to Ithaca and Tompkins County.
  - Vice Provost., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    Corson, Dale R.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Noyes, Jansen. Noyes Freshmen Center; Social Sciences Building; Housing; Faculty housing; Biology buildings location.
  - Vice Provost., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    Mackesey, Thomas W. Student conduct; Dormitories; Art museum; Faculty housing; Student housing.
  - Vice Provost., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    Mackesey, Thomas W.; Noyes, Jansen Sr. Noyes Freshman Center; University of Puerto Rico; Student housing; Dormitories; Social Sciences Building.
  - Vice Provost., 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    Mackesey, Thomas W. Savage Farm.
  - Planning Office., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Institutional Research, Studies., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Jackson, R. Peter. Office of Institutional Studies.
  - Office of Regional Planning and Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Doxiadis, Constantin; Houghton, Amory; Winston, Oliver C. Office of Regional Resources and Development.
  - Office of Regional Planning and Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Winston, Oliver C.; Rockefeller, Laurance S.; Houghton, Amory.
  - Office of Regional Planning and Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Winston, Oliver C. Ford Foundation,
  - Vice President for Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Muller, Steven; Clark, Van Alan; Olin, John M.; Olin, Spencer T.; Barlow, Mark. Ford Foundation; National Science Foundation; Constitutional Convention.
  - Vice President for Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Muller, Steven; Noyes, Jansen. Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art; Dormitory financing; Tuition.
  - Vice President for Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Muller, Steven; Noyes, Jansen. Ford Foundation; Society for the Humanities; Faculty Club.
  - Vice President for Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Muller, Steven; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Donlon, Mary H. Ford Foundation; University Faculty; Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art; Goldwin Smith Hall; Center for International Studies.
  - Vice President for Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Muller, Steven; Freund, Gerald. Samuel H. Kress Foundation; Rockefeller Foundation; University Committee on the Arts; College of Arts and Sciences; Center for International Studies; Student housing.
  - Office of Planning and Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Mackesey, Thomas W.; Trethaway, Edward J.; Ramin, Richard M.
  - Office of Planning and Development., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Trethaway, Edward J.; Haley, Rip; Ramin, Richard M. Tower Club; Foundation Newsletter; Centennial Campaign.
  - Alumni Directory., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Friend, James A.
  - Cornell University Council., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Muller, Steven. Cornell Daily Sun.
  - Cornell University Council., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Kochenour, Edith O.
  - Parents' Weekend., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Vice President for Research., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Long, Franklin A. American Council on Education; Conflicts of interest, government sponsored research at universities.
  - Vice President for Research., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Long, Franklin A.; Glennan, T. Keith. Social Science Research Center; Langmuir Laboratory; Federal grants.
  - Vice President for Research., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Long, Franklin A. Applied Research Institute at Cornell University (Proposed); United States Dept. of Defense; Federal grants; Computers.
  - Vice President for Research., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Long, Franklin A.; Pimentel, David. Ford Foundation; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; Materials Science Center; New York State College of Agriculture; Pimentel Report on the New York State College of Agriculture and its Future.
  - Vice President for Research., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Long, Franklin A.; Pimentel, David; Hill, Forest F. National Aeronautics and Space Administration; Pimentel Report; Federal funds; Computers.
  - Vice President for Business., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Vice President for Business., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Wood, Frederic C.; Burton, John E. Cornell University Industry Research Park; Projects underway.
  - Buildings and Properties., 1966 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    Weinhold, Julius F.
  - Housing Research Center., 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Cornell University Center for Housing and Environmental Studies.
  - Campus Store., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Safety Division and Traffic., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Herson, James M. Troian Horse.
  - Board on Traffic Control., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 28-30)
    Minutes.
  - Residential Halls, Dormitories., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Purchasing Dept., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Rogers, W.B.
  - Sage Chapel., 1967 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Residential Club fire.
  - Vice President for Student Affairs., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Barlow, Mark; Dean, Arthur H.; Stott, Richard B. Cornell United Religious Work (CURW); National Collegiate Athletic Association; United States Selective Service; University Commission on Residential Environment; Release of student records.
  - Vice President for Student Affairs., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Barlow, Mark. University Faculty; Interfraternity Council; Cornell University Residence Plan; Student demonstrations; United States Selective Service.
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Sproull, Robert L.; Cooke, W. Donald. Ford Foundation; Greek Civilization Program.
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Sproull, Robert L.; Cooke, W. Donald Center for Educational Research and Development.
  - Treasurer., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 38-39)
  - Academic Budgets., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 40-41)
  - Budget Director., 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 42-43)
    McKeegan, Paul L.
  - Secretary of the Corporation and University Counsel., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Stamp, Neal R.; Adams, Morton; Dean, Arthur H.
  - Secretary of the Corporation and University Counsel., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Stamp, Neal R.; Newman, Floyd R.; Upson, Maxwell: M.; Purcell, Robert W.; Cisler, Walker L. Committee on Long-range Financing; Student Housing Code; Cornell University Residence Plan.
  - Director of Admissions., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Secondary Schools Committee., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Admission., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    McCormick, John W.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Robles, Marcos A.
  - Applications for Admission., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Balik, Arthur.
  - Cornell Day., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Registrar., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 8-10)
    Williams, Herbert H.
  - Registration Figures., 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Baccalaureate and Commencement., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Controller., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Peterson, Arthur H.; Gould, Samuel B. Statutory colleges; WHCU.
  - Dean of Men and Women, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Davis, Stanley W.; Sheraw, Donald M.
  - International Student Office., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Kizilbash, Mehdi.
  - Students., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    CUSLAR (Cornell Committee for U.S. and Latin American Relations).
  - Fraternities and Interfraternity Council., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Konvitz, Milton R.; Berger, Samuel R.; Marcham, John; Trussell, John C.; Muka, Betty O.
  - Orientation Program., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Student Government Executive Board., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Brandt, David M.